westfield.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

This Privacy Policy ( **“Privacy Policy”** ) was last updated on July 13, 2015.

**_Our Policy:_**

This Privacy Policy sets forth the practices of Westfield Corporation and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively referred to as, “ **Westfield** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ” and/or “ **our** ”) with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“ **Personal**   **Data** ”) and other information that is collected from users of the Westfield websites and mobile applications that are owned and/or operated by Westfield in the United States, including, without limitation,  **[www.westfield.com](http://www.westfield.com/)** ,  **[www.bespokesf.co](http://www.bespokesf.co/)** , their subdomains, and optimized versions of these websites for mobile phones (collectively, together, with any other activities or services provided by Westfield whereby Westfield collects Personal Data, referred to as “ **Services** ”), including visitors to Westfield owned or managed malls, shopping centers and properties (collectively referred to as “Facility” or “Facilities”) and, such users and visitors (collectively referred to as “ **you** ” and “ **your** ”).

**_  
Information We Collect:_**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. When logging in with Facebook this information may include email address, birthday, gender, and your first name.

We may also collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

**Personal Data That You Provide to Us:**  includes your name, email address, phone number, gender, birthday, credit card information and billing address, or any other information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a you, or to identify you in context. This information is voluntarily provided to us, for example when you contact us with inquiries, respond to one of our surveys, sign up for promotions, sweepstakes or contests (“Promotions”), sign up for newsletters, register for access to the Services or use certain Services, sign up to order food at certain Westfield locations, use our WIFI services, use one of our interactive terminals at our Westfield facilities, or provide us with contact details in connection with the purchase of Westfield gift cards. Wherever we collect Personal Data on our websites or mobile applications we will provide a link to this Privacy Policy.

**By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to Westfield, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Westfield and the authorized third parties referred to herein. We will not share your Personal Data with third parties in ways that are not described in this Privacy Policy, unless your consent is obtained prior to doing so. This Privacy Policy also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Data and how you can access and update this information.**  You agree that we will not be held responsible or liable for the acts or omissions of any third party with whom we have shared your Personal Data.

**Other Information:**

**Non-Identifiable Data:**  When you interact with Westfield through the Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Westfield may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Westfield affiliates, agents or service providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Services, the number of visitors to each page of our Services, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.

In operating the Services, we along with our third party partners may use tracking technologies such as, without limitation, Cookies, E-Tags, JavaScript, Local Storage Objects (LSOs) HTML5 and Flash, and web beacons.

A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Services gives to your browser when you access the Services. Cookies help provide additional functionality to the Services and help us analyze Services usage more accurately. For instance, our Services may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Services without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Services. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. You may opt out of such tracking by clicking  **[here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/)**.

E-Tag is a technology that is part of the standard HTTP protocol that allows our website to validate temporary storage (cache) of our pages and images. This ensures that you are viewing the latest version of our website since your last visit.

JavaScript is a dynamic object oriented computer programming language. JavaScript is used to [understand user behavior on our website].

Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 and Flash to store [content information and preferences]. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs, but cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.. To manage Flash LSOs please click  **[here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager02.html)**.

Our third party partners also use web beacons, which is a clear graphic image of 1x1 pixel that is delivered through a web browser usually as part of a webpage request. Web beacons operate as a tag that records an end users visit to a particular webpage.

**Advertising**. We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [ **here**](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click  **[here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)** ). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

You may set a “Do Not Track” privacy preference in your web browsers. When you turn on “Do Not Track” in your browser, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to stop collecting the information that allows us to tailor suggestions based on your recent use of the Service and your visits to websites within our advertising partner networks. Specifically, we stop collecting the unique cookie that links your browser to use of the Service and visits to these websites for tailoring suggestions or ads.

**Aggregated Personal Data:**  In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services and visitors to our centers, we often conduct research on our customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and we may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

**Location Information:  **We may collect and use your location information (for example, by using the GPS on your mobile device or recognizing proximity to known Bluetooth transmitters (“beacons”)) to provide certain functionality of our Services. An example of such functionality would be to send special deals and discounts based on your location. If you choose to enable our location features, and if you choose to share that information publicly or with other users, your location information may be publicly displayed within the Services. We may also use your location information to provide you with personalized services, or in an aggregate way, as described above in the “Aggregated Personal Data” section. You may choose to opt-out of collection of mobile device location data by changing the settings on your mobile device or by following the instructions provided in the applicable shopping center and/or visiting [ **http://www.smartstoreprivacy.org/**](http://www.smartstoreprivacy.org/).

**Video and Camera Surveillance:  **Westfield shopping centers and parking lots may be under video and camera surveillance. When entering Westfield shopping centers and parking lots, your personal information and images may be collected by Westfield or by third parties on Westfield’s behalf, and Westfield may collect your personal information and images from third parties (for example, the police, retailers or third party service providers). This information may be used by Westfield in connection with the management and security of the Westfield shopping centers or for measuring and analyzing shopping behavior in order to improve our centers. This information may be provided to law enforcement, government bodies, Westfield staff, subcontractors, insurers, retailers and service providers for those purposes. The license plates of vehicles parked by customers in parking lots may also be collected and used for the above purposes and also to assist customers to locate their cars including via online and mobile applications.

**Use of Wi-Fi Systems:**  Wi-Fi services at all Westfield centers are provided either directly by us or by one of our third party Wi-Fi partners.

You may logon and use the Wi-Fi systems by providing your name and email address. We will use this information to keep you informed about upcoming Westfield events, activities, promotions, including sponsor and retailer promotion. Other information collected from your use of the Wi-Fi service can include websites visited.

In certain locations, we partner with third party service providers to give you Wi-Fi access. In such instances, the third party providers are the data controllers. When you access Wi-Fi systems at these locations, our third party partners will collect user information and provide this information to Westfield. The third party partners will continue to retain rights over the use of the data collected. The manner in which these third party partners use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of such third party partners. Westfield is not responsible for the use of any data collected by the third party service providers. To facilitate transparency, we will provide you with notice of such a relationship in the Terms and Services agreement that you agree to prior to using the applicable Wi-Fi services; we will also provide you with a link to both our privacy policy and that of our third party partners within the Terms and Service agreement before you logon to access the Wi-Fi service.

**Mobile Device Data:**  When you visit a Westfield shopping center, we and our third party providers may automatically collect certain information such as, without limitation, the operating system of your mobile device. None of your personally identifiable information such as name, phone number, email address or credit card information can be collected in this manner (other than when you voluntarily provide us that information via your mobile device in order to use certain Services). This information will be used to measure and analyze shopping behavior in order to improve our centers and otherwise in connection with our business. You may choose to opt-out of collection of mobile device data by following the instructions provided in the applicable shopping center and/or visiting [http://www.smartstoreprivacy.org/.](http://www.smartstoreprivacy.org/)

**Mobile Applications:**  You may choose to download our mobile applications such as “Westfield US” and “Dine on Time”. These applications may request to access to your location using GPS and/or network services or recognizing proximity to known Bluetooth transmitters (“beacons”). This information may be used to provide you with relevant information and for any other purpose that is in compliance with our Privacy Policy. We may use your Personal Data when you create an account on “Dine on Time” mobile application to process and deliver your order and for any other purpose that is in compliance with our Privacy Policy. We use a third party credit card processor to process your credit card information; when an order is placed. You agree that we will not be held responsible or liable for the acts or omissions of any such third party credit card processor. Our mobile applications may also send “Push Notifications” to your mobile device to provide updates and other relevant information. You may manage Push Notifications from the “settings” page within the mobile application or from your device’s settings tab.

**_Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information:_**

If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided and for any other purpose in compliance with our Privacy Policy. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Westfield may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Services and our shopping centers to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services and our shopping centers, to better understand our users and to improve the Services and our shopping centers. Westfield and its affiliates may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

If Westfield intends on using any Personal Data that has been collected by us in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

**_Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:_**

Westfield is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

**Business Transfers:**  As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses, assets or shopping centers including (but not limited to) marketing materials and data, customer data and lists, and all other information associated with the business, asset or shopping center. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, purchase or sale of assets (including without limitation the purchase or sale of a shopping center) or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets.

**Related Companies:  **We may also share your Personal Data with our affiliates and subsidiaries for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: Westfield, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

**Legal Requirements:**  Westfield may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation such as, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena, or a similar legal process (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Westfield, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services, visitors to our centers or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

**Promotions:**  We may share Personal Data that you provide in connection with a Promotion with our sponsors and advertisers. We may also share such data with our sponsors and advertisers so that they may send you other Promotions they offer, but only if you give us your permission to do so, and we will endeavor to share it only with that specific sponsor or advertiser.

_  
**Your Choices:**_

You can visit the Services and our centers without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain aspects of the Services.

**_Exclusions:_**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Westfield other than Personal Data collected through the methods listed above. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Westfield through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Westfield shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

**_Children:_**

Westfield does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data to Westfield. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Westfield, please contact us at  **[usprivacy@westfield.com](mailto:usprivacy@westfield.com)** , and we will delete that information from our databases.

**_Links to Other Websites:_**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services and Westfield owned and managed shopping centers. The Services and our centers may contain links to other websites or companies not operated or controlled by Westfield (the “Third Parties”). The policies and procedures we describe here do not apply to the Third Parties. The links from the Services or advertisements within the centers do not imply that Westfield endorses or has reviewed the Third Parties, or the Third Parties’ privacy practices. We suggest visiting Third Parties websites or contacting them directly for information on their privacy policies.

**_Integrating Social Networking Services:_**

We may integrate certain parts of our website with social networking sites such as Facebook, which allow you to post to our community forms and login when entering our sweepstakes (“Social Networking Service(s)”). By directly integrating these services, we make your online experiences richer and more personalized. To take advantage of this feature, we will ask you to log into or grant us permission via the relevant Social Networking Service. When you log into your Social Networking Services account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Service to access that Social Networking Service and your data contained within that Social Networking Service. As part of such integration, the Social Networking Service will provide us with access to certain information that you have provided to the Social Networking Service, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Networking Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of such third parties, and Company shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Social Networking Services that may be enabled within the Service. You may also have the option of posting your Services activities to Social Networking Services when you access content through the Services (for example, you may post to Facebook that you performed an activity on the Service); you acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers and subscribers on any Social Networking Services you have enabled will be able to view such activity.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our website includes Social Media Widgets such as the Twitter, Facebook, Pinterest, and YouTube. These widgets allow you to visit, share and interact with Westfield pages on their respective platforms. These features may collect your IP address, which pages you are visiting, and may set a cookie to enable features to function properly. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature.

**Framing/Masking**

Some of our pages utilize framing or masking techniques to serve content to or from our partners such as blog postings and sweepstakes or promotions, while preserving the look and feel of our site. Please be aware that you are providing your personal information to these third parties, and not Westfield.

**_Security:_**

The security of your personal information is important to us. Westfield takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided to us from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). However, no data or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. For example, email sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Westfield.

**_Other Terms and Conditions:_**

Your access to and use of the Services is subject to the Terms of Service at ** http://www.westfield.com/us/help/terms-conditions**.

**_Changes to Westfield’s Privacy Policy:_**

The Services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Westfield to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Westfield reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by means of a notice on this website. Your continued use of the Services or visits to our centers after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

**_  
TRUSTe Privacy Program_**

Westfield has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program only covers information that may be collected on  **[www.westfield.com](http://www.westfield.com/)** , **[www.bespokesf.co,](http://www.bespokesf.co/)**  their subdomain, and optimized versions of these websites for mobile phones and our mobile applications “Westfield US” and “Dine on Time,”

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at  **[usprivacy@westfield.com](mailto:usprivacy@westfield.com)**  or at the address listed below. If you are not satisfied with our response, you can contact TRUSTe at ** <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>**.

Please click  **[here](http://www.truste.com/about-TRUSTe/contact-us)**  for fax and postal mail information. TRUSTe's Dispute Resolution process is only available in English.

**_Access to Information and Choice; Contacting Westfield:_**

If your personal information changes you may email us to have it corrected, updated, amended, or removed at [ **usprivacy@westfield.com**](mailto:usprivacy@westfield.com) or send the inquiry by postal mail at the address listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days of submission.

**Data Retention:  **We will retain your information including geo-location for as long as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Westfield’s Privacy Policy.

You may contact us as follows:

Westfield Labs Corporation  
835 Market Street, Suite 517  
San Francisco, CA 94103  
United States of America  
Attention: Director of Privacy  
Email:  **[usprivacy@westfield.com](mailto:usprivacy@westfield.com)**
